The End
Father, after spending some
time behind these stone walls,
I've come to realize how
foolish I was in the past.
My desire to steal consumed me,
and from there I lost all control.
I am deeply ashamed.
It's all thanks to you, Father.
And so, may I please have your
assistance in receiving early parole?
Recent studies show that if they
receive the proper training,
animals such as dogs and parrots
can learn to read, use fire,
and even appreciate art.
If that's truly the case, then what's the
difference between humans and animals?
Do you know?
Well, yeah, of course.
However, I don't see how
that relates to my...
Ah, just a moment.
Father?
It's done.
Have you ever tried this?
The challenge comes after completing the
first cherry with it still in your mouth.
Now which tooth must you
use to bite into the second?
If you accidentally
bit the first seed that
you went through the
trouble of completing,
it wouldn't end well.
Uh-huh.
Anyway, sorry, Father,
but about my parole?
Hmm.
I think there is a possibility.
Do you really mean it, Father?
I will be sure to put in a good
word for you with the committee.
Thank you very much!
I have taken a liking to
those mischievous hands.
Your ill-natured self will never be fixed.
But I cannot ignore the
talents you possess.
They will be of much use to me.
By no means can Jotaro
Stan leave this prison,
so I will leave the task
of preventing that to you.
I don't want to say no time, let's go.
1,2,3 Can we find a way?
5, 4, 3
We're coming low
time I don't stop beating,
don't stop beating, don't
stop beating, I'm up!
What?
The hell do you mean you had
FF hide it somewhere for you?
After all that effort it took to get
it, it's got your dad's stand on it.
Sure, that's okay.
Do you even know where it is?
I mean, they're still in...
This place is so fun!
Compared to the swamp, it's lovely.
Seriously?
We should do what
they're doing over there.
I think it's called playing catch, right?
Look, I trust FF.
And as far as we know, Pale Snake
has no clue our new friend's alive.
It's safer this way.
Yeah, guess you're right.
But look at it like this,
wouldn't it be even better to send
it to the people holding your dad?
It would.
Thing is,
I tried to escape so my phone
and visitor privileges are gone,
and I still haven't come up
with a plan to carry it out.
Hey, you fugly ho!
Take that out of your mouth now!
Huh?
What did you just say to me?
I replenish my thirst
and you hurl insults?
Put the cup down now!
They're on the bench where
you found it, immediately!
If it's that important to you, you
shouldn't leave it sitting around,
especially in a place like this.
Just ignore her!
We'll go get you more water!
It's okay, FF, don't make a scene!
Please!
Give it here! Huh?
Well, I guess it's okay.
There's actually more here now. Lucky me!
All right.
Let's throw the ball around, yeah? What?
Good grief.
You've never thrown a ball, have you?
Uh-oh.
Nah, pull your hips back in.
A little more.
There you go, looking good, right?
Jolene, did you know?
We've gone back and
forth 86 times already.
We haven't dropped it once!
Think we'll hit a hundred?
A hundred dollars says you won't. Huh?
Will you take that bet?
Sorry, but who are you?
And what are you saying?
My name is Mirashon, and
FE26789 is my prisoner number.
I'm saying you won't catch the ball.
I'm willing to bet a hundred dollars!
that your little game of catch?
will end before you reach a hundred.
Don't you think this is
coming out of nowhere?
What do you really want?
Just trying to kill time.
Let's do it!
It's only 13 more passes!
Hey, not another word, you!
Regardless,
I don't have anywhere near that amount of
money on me, so it won't be much of a bet.
Well, it doesn't have
to be money, you know.
I'll take drugs, cigarettes, chewing gum,
some phone time, hell, even a vibrator.
Anything with a bit of value will do.
I'll be frank with you.
I don't really do bets, so get lost.
Wait just a second.
Come on, Jolene.
You should go along with this.
We've got some crazy luck, and
whatever you don't have, I'll lend you.
FF sucks at throwing, but they've
managed to do it 87 times.
We can win.
There's more to it than that.
Yeah, it might be a trap
set by Palesnake, right?
But I know that Mira shown.
We're on the same floor together.
She's a stupid gambler that ruined
her life committing small robberies.
Think about it for a sec.
When you're finally able to
use the phones and get visits,
you're definitely going to wish you had
this money to buy your place in line.
Hey, are you in or are
you not? Count me in!
I want to do it for sure!
We can totally win!
Okay, but do you even have $100 on you?
We'll play,
but conditions are if you raise your voice
or move even one step from that spot,
the bet is called off.
Got it?
So the game has already begun then, huh?
But it won't be fair
if the distance is too
close or if you hold on
to the ball for too long.
More than three meters
apart, within ten seconds.
Okay.
All right, let's get this thing started!
Just calm down before you throw.
You've got ten seconds, so take your time.
And that makes 89.
Now there's only 11 more to go.
You little...
Get those sticky fingers the
hell away from my water! Hey!
Way too close.
Concentrate, damn it!
That's not it!
She's the problem here!
What is she doing near my water?
I'm just spectating quietly.
Well, do it away from my cup or else!
Fine, whatever.
Clock's ticking. Go,
Ephef! Throw the ball!
Screw this girl!
She's bugging me!
I'll hold your water, now throw the ball!
One second.
Throw it! Shit!
Idiot!
Joey!
That was close, but you pulled through.
I'm sorry.
I panicked back there.
Be more careful next time, FF.
Yeah, right. I'm fine now.
Here we go!
That was a hundred times! Okay.
With the way I'm feeling, a hundred
more times sounds like a breeze, too!
It was an easy win like I thought.
Now fork over the hundred dollars.
No.
You were betting with FF
earlier, too, weren't you?
So doesn't that mean it
should be two hundred?
Yeah, true.
It definitely should be two hundred.
Hurry up and give it to me.
I've got a grand on you not
being able to do it again.
What, did you not hear me?
I'm telling you my bet is $1,000.
Are you for real?
Do you even have that kind of cash?
Of course.
But like I said earlier,
anything with value will
do the trick just the same.
The rules remain unchanged
as well. Sound good?
No, we're done with your games.
We might have just won.
But honestly, I don't like you one bit.
So if you want to bet,
take it somewhere else.
I'll go instead of her.
Well, okay. Abs, here!
Give me the bowling glove!
On it! Irvis!
Jolene, I don't like this
chick all that much either.
Or the way she's oddly fixated on betting.
But still, if it's going to be
$1,200 including the earlier bet,
there's no way we can pass this up.
You might want to be careful.
Like the rules of the last game, this
one began the moment you decided to play.
You've less than 10 seconds. Throw it!
I'm in your way!
It's another easy victory!
30!
31!
32!
Nice!
Next we'll be a 33!
Huh?
That's enough!
Put away the gear already!
Today's exercise period is over!
Five seconds.
F's catch!
33!
The hell's your damage?
We're not gonna have ourselves
a problem here, are we?
Hey, you!
We're calling this bed off!
It's done!
Okay, here's a thought for you.
Let's suppose for a moment now that a
meteorite fell from the
heavens out of nowhere.
Sure, it's wild,
but you'd probably think that the game
should be called off, like it's just over.
You'd say it's the Meteor's fault.
And not to convince me,
mind you, but yourselves.
But are you sure that's okay?
Don't you think you two might
have run out of exercise time?
Because you were taking your sweet time
and deliberately throwing the ball slowly?
Take a good look into
your heart and you'll see.
If it's telling you you didn't break
any rules, there's no need to worry.
By all means, if you're innocent,
you can stop the game at any time.
Fuck you!
That's it, Armas!
Be prepared to be sent
to solitary confinement!
Please, Mr.
Guard, just this once.
Five minutes.
No, three will do.
Two minutes.
I'm gonna go make my rounds over here.
Fs, now! Hurry up!
But a measly $100 will only go so far.
I'd say it only covers the ball.
I'll be taking that
glove. Give it her! What?
Dammit!
Ah, shit!
But in case something like this might
happen, I'd put a sticker on there.
Hermes, no!
Let's keep going.
I'm merely a spectator here.
I won't move a muscle or even think.
But still, though I can't
prove what she just did.
On the inside, Ermes knows
exactly what happened.
There's no denying it.
Your bestie just broke one of the rules.
I know because the debt collector, Mary
Lynn Manson, has appeared before us.
Hermes, hey! Watch yourself!
She's a stand user!
No matter where you hide it
away or what the item is,
it takes absolutely everything
and leaves nothing behind.
This is still not enough.
Sticker!
Game over.
Hermes!
If you sold this liver I'm
holding on the Black Market,
It would make up for the
remaining $590 that you owe.
Piss off! Oh, shit!
I am the shadow that lies
deep within Hermes' heart.
The two of you cannot
possibly land an attack on me.
Hermes has broken the
rules you established,
and has therefore lost the bet on her own.
I came to collect the debt
weighing on her shoulders.
Or are there any other
precious items she may have?
If so, I can exchange this liver
for something of equal value.
This bet still isn't over yet. What?
We'll catch the ball a thousand times.
And if we succeed, you'll give
back everything you took from her.
And then just leave us
the hell alone. Okay.
However, I'm sure you're
aware of how this goes.
You must offer something of equal value.
Yeah, I know. Excellent.
With the rules set, the game has begun.
See you later.
Esa, here!
J-Jolene!
Ermes, you're not the one at fault here.
Since Miraschon is a stand user, there's
a high chance that Palesnake is involved.
If that's the case, then they're
aiming for my dad's disc.
That's what the Collector is for.
There you go.
Another reason not to take this bet.
You got dragged into this shit
fest because of my family drama.
I can't let you die for me.
But how the hell are we
going to pull this off?
We're talking about a
thousand throws in a row.
And that thing earlier
was basically invincible.
Yeah, that's exactly why.
We're going to chase down
Miroshon and attack her directly.
That greedy stand of hers may be
invincible, but her body is fair game.
That's why she's putting
distance between us.
Let's go!
You see her?
I'm sure I saw her come in here.
That door on the other side of the room.
She must have left from there.
Pass into you.
Jolene.
Wait!
Don't throw!
Seriously!
Shut up!
As I threw the ball.
Yeah!
But where?
I can't see a damn thing.
Don't move!
It'll probably hit your body.
It's okay!
I got the ball! That's great, FF!
Now let's just stay calm
and keep the ball moving!
Over here!
Where the hell is here? Hurry!
It's already over.
I'm right here!
Now I'm angry!
You're fighting a fool.
I heard a voice come from
somewhere over there.
So I fired randomly in
that general direction.
Damn it.
What the fuck is that thing?
We are now nearing lockdown time.
All prisoners must return
to their cells immediately
and remain standing until
the roll call begins.
I repeat, the roll call
will commence shortly.
Look, she ran that way!
How unfortunate for you.
There's nowhere left to run.
And now that I know you're a fellow
stand user, I won't need to hold back.
Hey, wait a second.
Take the money, and deliver.
Here, it's all yours!
That's not the only thing I want.
For starters, I want to know who in
this prison gave you stand power.
It was Palesnake, right? Don't lie.
Tell me who they really are.
What are you talking about?
You sure you got time to be playing dumb?
You gotta believe me!
I don't know who that is!
All I wanted to do was go on parole!
This is...
An elevator.
One that transports our meals.
How much longer now?
Six seconds?
Or is it five?
No!
Julian!
Two more.
FF, the ball!
Come on, FF, throw it here!
Shit!
Nice job.
Now what are you gonna do?
You've got eight more seconds.
Seven.
Six.
Catch him now!
This is what you wanted.
Ain't that right, Mirachon?
Taking care of easy and convenient
favors like this is nothing for me.
Need anything else?
Just give me a call.
Try catching the ball now!
Oh, you can't anymore, can you?
This game of catch is over!
You're dead, Jolyne Keicho!
Mary Lynn Manson will always
come to collect what is owed!
No matter where they may be hidden.
Even if you are unaware,
Mary Lynn will know!
Jolene!
First, I'll take your
most expensive organ.
And to cover the remainder, I'll
take your most precious possession.
Your father's stand disc.
As for where to find it...
That psychotic brat FF has had it
behind them since the very beginning!
I won!
Now I've got your organ and your disc!
It all belongs to me!
This little game of
catch is far from over.
But how?
The ball?
Impossible.
Cheater no, I never actually specified
the person I'd be playing catch with.
The guard counts too?
Seems like the collector also improves.
Now that we have 800 more
balls to catch or was it 900?
You know what? Screw it!
I'm gonna get my dad's
disc out of this prison.
And that includes the one
Palesnake's holding on to.
Just watch.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place
other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.